<resources>
    <string name="app_name">VG Tier List</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="category_top">Top</string>
    <string name="category_mid">Mid</string>
    <string name="category_bot">Bot</string>
    <string name="category_captain">Cap</string>
    <string name="category_jungle">Jun</string>


    <!-- Hero Descriptions -->

    <string name="ardan">Ardan is a damage-soaking protector who dramatically changes the landscape
        of teamfights. Able to rescue friends from certain death and turn lost battles around with
        his powerful terrain-changing ultimate, Ardan brings immense utility to the team.</string>

    <string name="grumpjaw">Grumpjaw is a durable fighter, able to last in battles while maintaining
        stacks of his Living Armor through basic attacks. Grumpjaw can charge headlong into a fight,
        heavily damaging and slowing enemies at the end of his charge. Once he breaks through enemy
        lines, Grumpjaw can easily turn the tides of battle by devouring one of his enemies and
        briefly removing them from the fight.</string>

    <string name="yates">Yates is a battlefield commander with a global presence. Yates is the kind
        of captain that knows how to make an appearance. Whenever his allies are in need of help, he
        can leap to their aid regardless of where they are on the map.</string>

    <string name="flicker">Flicker is a sneaky trickster able to disrupt foes with his debilitating
        abilities. Utilizing his stealth, Flicker can plunge deep into enemy lines causing mayhem or
        grant his team stealth to initiate on unsuspecting prey.</string>

    <string name="reza">Reza is a fast, devastating fire mage with a demon netherform. Reza melts
        his enemies by chaining his abilities into devastating combos. His exceptional mobility
        coupled with high burst damage allows him to dance on the edge of fights or chase down
        fleeing enemies with ease.</string>

    <string name="anka">Anka is an elusive and bursty assassin who strikes with a flurry of blades.
        Anka specializes in taking out vulnerable carries with surgical precision. When she has a
        mark, nothing can keep her target safe from the cold steel of her blade.</string>

    <string name="tony">Tony is a dwarven brawler who taunts and pummels enemies.</string>

    <string name="catherine">Catherine brings the most reliable stun and disruption skills to
        teamfights and ganks. Hard to kill and great at chasing, she can secure kills and turn
        around fights that would otherwise be lost.</string>

    <string name="lance">Lance depends on both his courage and his wits to protect his allies. With
        his unique polearm-and-shield combat style, he breaks enemy lines and creates opportunities
        for his friends. Lance can build crystal or utility items to excel in his role as a
        protector, or he can build weapon items to deal more damage during battle.</string>

    <string name="adagio">Adagio can heal. He can amplify damage. He can stun and nuke the entire
        enemy team. This master manipulator of large-scale battles brings shines through
        area-of-effect damage and team-saving abilities.</string>

    <string name="lorelai">Lorelai is a happy sea creature that excels at zone
        control and team utility</string>

    <string name="vox">Vox is a mobile sniper with a high-energy playstyle, able to quickly and
        frequently dash around the battlefield. Vox deals significant damage either to a single
        target or to groups of enemies depending on his build. This allows Vox to react to the
        needs of his team.</string>

    <string name="skye">Skye is a swift sniper able to dance at the edge of fights or dive deep into
        the enemy backline to kill key targets. Skye’s unique strafing attacks change the complexion
        of fights, and her ability to chase down and catch opponents is unparalleled.</string>

    <string name="blackfeather">Blackfeather is a striking duelist who pierces the hearts of his
        opponents. When building weapon items, he becomes a powerful assassin. Building crystal and
        utility items instead unlocks powerful effects for himself and his team. He performs well in
        the lane where he can focus on accumulating gold early in the match.</string>

    <string name="joule">Joule is a hardened front-line fighter with built-in defensive plating. All
        of Joule\'s abilities require proper aim to hit the intended target, but they have a 
        devastating effect if you can aim properly. Pick Joule if you can 
        predict enemy movements.</string>

    <string name="malene">Malene is a form-swapping spellcaster who deals massive crystal damage with light
        and shadow abilities. She can switch into her Light Form to provide utility for her team or
        into her Shadow Form to devastate her enemies</string>

    <string name="skaarf">Skaarf blazes his way through the fold, incinerating everything in his
        path. He specializes in powerful abilities that set his enemies on fire, bringing them down
        from a distance.</string>

    <string name="celeste">Celeste lights the way for her team, calling upon her stars for both
        artillery and long-range reconnaissance. Though fragile, she is well-suited to fighting from
        the furthest edges of battle.</string>

    <string name="samuel">Samuel is a dark mage who controls large areas with his abilities. Samuel
        is able to deal damage on the move, but he may be caught out of position if played too
        aggressively. He is well suited in the lane, able to bully his victim while draining health
        and energy to sustain himself.</string>

    <string name="varya">Varya is a shocking valkyrie who chains massive damage across enemy teams.
        She wields lethal lightning that can leap between enemy heroes and leaves them as shaking
        burned out husks.</string>

    <string name="baron">Baron rains destruction on his opponents. When building crystal items, he
        becomes mobile artillery, laying siege to enemy teams. His weapon path enables aggressive
        in-your-face tactics. No matter how he builds, he brings incredible range and powerful burst
        damage to any team.</string>

    <string name="lyra">Lyra draws upon her training as a Gythian battlemage to use healing and
        protective magic to turn enemy positions into powerful zones for her allies. Her portals 
        also allow her team to bypass these positions entirely, avoiding defenses and terrain. 
        Utility and defense items improve her role as a healer, while crystal items provide a 
        devastating but fragile mage path.</string>

    <string name="kinetic">Kinetic is a nimble duelist wielding a powerful pulse cannon. SHe is a
        ranged carry who exerts her dominance in extended team fights. Once she fully charges her
        pulse cannon, she is capable of overwhelming any for with an endless
        barrage of energy blasts.</string>

    <string name="kestrel">Kestrel is an elite Stormguard archer who takes down targets from a 
        distance. When building weapon, she deals rapid, sustained damage and uses stealth to find 
        better footing when enemies get too close. Kestrel’s crystal path affords longer stealth 
        times, which sets up aggressive tactical plays. She’s best in the lane where she can use the
        protection of her turret to safely collect gold.</string>

    <string name="gwen">Gwen moves swiftly across the map, picking off enemies from a distance. She
        can shake off negative effects inflicted by her enemies, turning the tables in her favor.
        Gwen is best played in the lane where she can earn gold and gear up for big fights.</string>

    <string name="saw">SAW has arguably the highest damage potential in the game, but at the huge
        expense of mobility. Excellent at sieging important locations, SAW zones, slows and damages
        with Suppressing Fire.</string>

    <string name="silvernail">Silvernail is a grizzled hunter with a powerful crossbow and
        tripwires. He specializes in separating the battlefield through smart placement
        of his tripwires</string>

    <string name="ringo">Ringo is often played as the primary damage dealer for his team. He can 
        shoot at blinding speeds and finish off fleeing enemies with an epic fireball that follows 
        foes across the battlefield.</string>

    <string name="idris">Idris shifts through battle, piercing his targets with his spear and
        chakrams. When building weapon items he excels at assassinating vulnerable targets at close
        range, while crystal items allow him to dance around the fight, keeping his distance.
        Whether building weapon, crystal, or a combination of the two, Idris brings extraordinary
        damage and agility to any fight.</string>

    <string name="kensei">Kensei is an agile swordmaster who excels at fighting
        durable heroes</string>

    <string name="glaive">Glaive is a devastating powerhouse, instantly dashing into the action and
        knocking enemies into danger. His damage is devastating, but he is vulnerable to slippery
        opponents.</string>

    <string name="rona">Rona is a deadly berserker who is always ready to leap into battle.
        She holds her own in melee combat, unleashing enormous damage. Rona is best played in the
        jungle, pairs well with protectors and works well with both weapon
        and crystal builds.</string>

    <string name="churnwalker">Churnwalker is a disruptor who throws multiple skillshot hooks,
        chaining victims to him.</string>

    <string name="phinn">Phinn is an unstoppable tank who brings the fight to him. He pairs
        incredibly well with other heroes who don\'t back down from battle. Phinn is strongest
        with defense and utility items, and he\'s able to absorb immense amounts of punishment,
        protecting teammates while they dish out damage.</string>

    <string name="grace">Grace utilizes the power of the light to protect her allies by granting
        them Holy Shields that greatly reduce incoming damage. If the fight seems bleak, she can
        turn the tides of battle by calling upon the Seraphim to bring her allies back from the
        brink of death</string>

    <string name="fortress">This Halcyon Well guardian is a snarling, frightening sight in the 
        jungle. He stalks prey, closes in with teammates, flanks targets and creates challenging, 
        multi-front confrontations. Stay near your allies and bite and claw 
        your way to kills.</string>

    <string name="krul">Krul is a jungle nightmare who dominates in 1v1 duels. Able to absorb
        massive amounts of damage and recover large portions of health, Krul can bring the pain and
        survive a beating.</string>

    <string name="alpha">Alpha hunts and terminates her targets with ruthless precision. No longer
        bound to the rules of mortality, she engages in battle without fear or caution. Alpha
        performs well in the jungle and can take down her targets built either
        weapon or crystal.</string>

    <string name="koshka">Koshka is an in-your-face assassin adept at getting the kill and then
        getting out. She should focus on assassinating weak targets and locking down
        the most lethal enemy.</string>

    <string name="reim">Reim is a grumpy old winter mage who freezes everyone who crosses him.
        Though he moves slowly, he deals heavy damage to opponents while being surprisingly
        resilient himself. He holds his own in the lane, but he’s particularly effective in the
        jungle where he can go toe-to-toe against most opponents that he can catch.</string>

    <string name="baptiste">Baptiste dictates battle by striking fear into the heart of his
        enemies. Reaping the souls of his opponents, he both sustains himself and empowers his
        attacks and abilities. He commands his army of shades to either lock down unsuspecting
        victims or terrorize entire teams, forcing them to flee from him.</string>

    <string name="taka">Taka weaves through the battlefield, eliminating targets with his 
        switchblades. He lives on the knife\'s edge, compensating for fragile defenses with 
        agility and stealth.</string>

    <string name="ozo">Quick and nimble, Ozo leaps from hero to hero as he bounces around the
        battlefield. He is at home in the center of a chaotic fight where he can deal large amounts
        of area-of-effect damage. Remember to build defensive items to maximize the amount of time
        he can stay in combat.</string>

    <string name="petal">Petal plants seeds that slowly heal her and her friends. She can grow these
        seeds into minions that fight alongside her, and she can blow them up to obliterate
        vulnerable targets.</string>

</resources>